acemarks.com 2017-04-15

# Privacy Policy for Ace Marks

Ace Marks has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our visitors and customers. Ace Marks is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of the information you share with us. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you when you visit our site how we collect and use such information.

Section 1: What do we do with your information?

In general, you may visit many pages of the site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit the Website and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous unless they voluntarily tell us who they are.

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address, as well as any other information you volunteer during the purchase process.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about your order, our store, new products and other updates.

Section 2: Consent

How we get your consent:

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How to withdraw your consent:

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at help@acemarks.com or mailing us at:

Ace Marks, LLC.   
2401 NW 93rd Ave

Doral, FL 33172

Section 3: Disclosure

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service. Your information will not be sold or disclosed to third party marketers.

Section 4: Payments

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Authorize.net stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Authorize.net’s Terms of Service [here](http://www.authorize.net/company/terms/) or Privacy Statement [here](https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/).

Section 5: Third-Party Services

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

Google analytics:

Our store uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits our site and what pages are being looked at.

Section 6: Security

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

Section 7: Cookies

The site uses cookie technology to improve the quality of your experience. A cookie is a small file that contains information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your computers browser. Cookies store information that a website may need in order to personalize your experience and gather website statistical data. The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name

| 

COOKIE Description  
  
---|---  
  
CART

| 

The association with your shopping cart.  
  
CATEGORY_INFO

| 

Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
  
COMPARE

| 

The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
  
CURRENCY

| 

Your preferred currency  
  
CUSTOMER

| 

An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
  
CUSTOMER_AUTH

| 

An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
  
CUSTOMER_INFO

| 

An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS

| 

Stores the Customer Segment ID  
  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE

| 

A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
  
FRONTEND

| 

You session ID on the server.  
  
GUEST-VIEW

| 

Allows guests to edit their orders.  
  
LAST_CATEGORY

| 

The last category you visited.  
  
LAST_PRODUCT

| 

The most recent product you have viewed.  
  
NEWMESSAGE

| 

Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
  
NO_CACHE

| 

Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART

| 

A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
  
POLL

| 

The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
  
POLLN

| 

Information on what polls you have voted on.  
  
RECENTLYCOMPARED

| 

The items that you have recently compared.  
  
STF

| 

Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
  
STORE

| 

The store view or language you have selected.  
  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE

| 

Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS

| 

The products that you have recently viewed.  
  
WISHLIST

| 

An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
  
WISHLIST_CNT

| 

The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
PREF, persistent for a very short period, set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from where.

Section 8: Age of Consent

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

In other words, children (under the age of 18) should not use this site unsupervised, and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under the age of the age of consent, you may only use this site in conjunction with, and under the supervision of, your parents or guardians.

Section 9: Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

Questions and Contact Information

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at help@acemarks.com or by mail at:

Ace Marks, LLC   
2401 NW 93rd Ave   
Doral, FL 33172
